A Guide to the Files on the Kaleidoscope Center for Cultural Fluency
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Files on the Kaleidoscope Center for Cultural Fluency
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/16.091
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.)
Acquisition Information
The files were an archival transfer from the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life, 2009 May 13.
Scope and Content
Topics include the annual report, art exhibits, student interns, programs, reservations and scheduling of events, and strategic events. A scrapbook documenting activities, 2004-2005, is included.
The collection also contains a DVD of the movie "White noise" regarding activities of the center and a disk of art work by [Matt Owens?].
Contents List
- 2004-2005 Annual Report, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:1)
- 2005-2006 Annual Report, (3 items) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 2004-2005 Art Exhibits, (7 items) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 2005-2006 Art Exhibits, (13 items) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 2005 Art Exhibits - Gidey Gezahey, (3 items) (Box-folder 1:5)
- 2004-2006 Budget, (6 items) (Box-folder 1:6)
- 2005-2006 Intern - Bellinger, Christopher, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:7)
- 2005 Intern - Guo, Alyssa, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:8)
- 2005 Intern - Jackson, Gregory Neal, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:9)
- 2005 Intern - Juliano, Laura, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:10)
- 2005-2006 Intern- McLamore, Claire, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:11)
- 2005-2006 Intern - Shaw, Stephanie, (2 items) (Box-folder 1:12)
- 2005-2006 Intern - Simon, Candace, A., (1 items) (Box-folder 1:13)
- 2005-2006 Internship Requirements, (7 items) (Box-folder 1:14)
- 2005 Intern Welcoming Letters, (3 items) (Box-folder 1:15)
- 2004-2006 Lounge Nights, (15 items) (Box-folder 1:16)
- 2004-2006 Management, (10 items) (Box-folder 1:17)
- 2004 May 7 Memorandum from the Planning Committee, (1 items) (Box-folder 1:18)
- 2006 Feb Newsletter, (1 items) (Box-folder 1:19)
- 2006 Mar Peace Corps, (5 items) (Box-folder 1:20)
- 2004-2005 Programs, (10 items) (Box-folder 1:21)
- 2005-2006 Programs, (9 items) (Box-folder 2:1)
- 2004-2006 Promotions, (9 items) (Box-folder 2:2)
- 2005 Research, (2 items) (Box-folder 2:3)
- 2004-2006 Reservations, (7 items) (Box-folder 2:4)
- 2004 Reservations and Scheduling Guideline (Box-folder 2:5)
- 2004-2006 Resources, (9 items) (Box-folder 2:6)
- 1996;2004-2006 Strategic Planning, (10 items) (Box-folder 2:7)
- 2004-2005 Scrapbook, (oversize)